(Jack) Where is he?
他在那里？
(Jack) He's a French dealer selling a case of liquid heroin.
他是法国毒枭卖一箱液态海洛英
Ben, grab the drugs. Bobby's at the money.
本，提药。保比抓钱。
Me and Marshall will cover you till you get back to the car.
我和马歇尔掩护你回车。
Then we get the fuck out.
然后尽快闪脱。
So my plan, basically.
用我的基本计划。
You came to me, remember?
是你找我的 记得吗？
That's him.
是他。
Bobby.
保比。
Sorry, mate.
抱歉，老弟。
(Jack) Bobby.
保比。
Fuck.
狗日的。
(Marshall) Jack. Bobby.
杰克。  保比。
Bobby is gone, Jack. We need to leave now.
保比挂了，杰克，快闪。
Come on. Come on, now.
现在快撤。
Hi.
嗨。
Hi, sweetie pie.
嗨，小可爱。
How's my beautiful godson?
我美丽的教子怎样？
Yes.
是的。
[Whispering] Come here.
来。
Hi, sweet pie.
嗨，小可爱。
I missed you.
我想你。
You're late. Now I'm going to be late.
你迟到。现在我也耽误了。
Nice to see you, too.
见到你开心。
Someone has been crying his little head off all morning.
有人哭了整个上午。
The bloody washing machine's broken.
洗衣机坏了。
I'm having to wash everything in the sink.
要整个除臭。
Speaking of which-- don't push your luck, mommy.
谈到哪个 - 别赌你的运气，妈妈。
Godmothers babysit, we buy presents, we don't do laundry.
只照顾孩子，  我们买礼物，管不上洗涤。
Someone's very grumpy.
有人发脾气的。
You got your period? No.
来经了？没。
It's Sushi night, actually.
实际上是寿司夜。
You're not still doing that, are you? Yeah.
难道还在搞？  是的。
You might as well wear a t-shirt saying,
干脆穿件有字的衬衫
"hi, I'm ovulating. Do you want to fuck?"
"嗨，我正排卵期 要做爱吗？ "
What's the romance in that? Darling, you do know, if I had the money, I'd--
有啥好浪漫？  亲爱的，如果我有钱， 可以 --
well, actually, I'd first go buy a new washing machine,
嗯，但我得先买新洗衣机，
but then after that I'd pay for you to go private.
之后才能私下帮你分担。
I'd ivf you a baby.
让你怀上孩子。
How's tom?
汤姆如何？
He's just spending every waking minute at the house.
消耗每分钟整新屋。
You're so lucky to have him.
你真幸运有他。
And you're so lucky to have him.
你也幸运有他。
(Mike) Tom. Tom.
汤姆。  汤姆。
You up there?
在上头吗？
What you doing? Didn't you hear me?
干啥？没听到我吗？
Job I just finished had a little extra.
刚挣了点外快。
Thought you could use them.
你该用得上吧。
You all right, mate?
没事吧，兄弟？
I think we're going to lose the house. Oh, shit.
我会失掉房子。噢，大便。
I thought you were coming along. Yeah.
以为你单独忙。是的。
Not far enough.
还不够。
Pumped all the money into it.
把钱都投这。
Half my budget went into this fucking dry rot.
一半预算在狗日贷利。
What does Anna say?
安娜怎说？
I haven't told her, yet.
没告诉她。
She only knows half of what I spent and she's already freaking out.
只知道我花了一半，她已经在借支了。
We're trying to start a family. Can't even afford the rent on our apartment.
全在为了生儿育女。公寓房租都负担不了。
Just talk to her, mate. She'll understand.
兄弟 跟她商量会体谅。
Come on.
拜托。
If you're up for it, a friend of mine needs some painting done next week.
打起精神 下礼拜我朋友有油漆活。
Won't pay much, but--
价钱给不高，但--
yeah. Thanks.
好呗。谢啦。
It's a good thing I have a master's degree. Come in handy.
我有硕士学位还算过得去。
See you, bud.
再见，老兄。
Tom Wright? Yeah.
汤姆．莱特吗？  是的。
You're served.
催缴单。
We've got two weeks?
只剩两周了吗？
Thanks.
谢谢。
Ben.
本。
Turn it down.
小声点。
(Anna) Hello?
好吗？
Hi.
嗨。
It's, uh, Sushi night?
噢，寿司夜？
You forgot.
忘记了。
No. No.
没。
I never forget Sushi night. It's fine.
从未忘记 寿司夜 太好了。
Nice wine.
好酒。
It was just a few quid extra.
特价品。
A very nice wine. And I thought it was worth it.
非常好的酒 值得的。 word by BEE
Of course it's worth it.
当然值。
Come here.
来。
Sushi night.
寿司夜。
How's Julian?
朱利安怎样？
He's...Loud and--
哭声嘹亮--
tonight, yeah?
今晚，是吗？
Someone's going to get pregnant.
有人会怀孕。
Hey.
嘿。
You okay?
还好吗？
We're going to lose the house.
房子会赔掉。
No.
不。
No. We're going to work it out.
我会解决。
Mike just got me a few days on a good job.
麦克刚刚找我干几天活。
Maybe it's time we go back. No.
会赶上抵付。
No. Tom.
不 汤姆。
This was my idea.
是我的想法。
I promised you a fresh start.
答应过你新的开始。
I promised you a place to start a family.
有新居生儿育女。
That was then.
那是以前。
I'm not giving up.
我没放弃。
So...You can shut up.
所以你闭嘴。
[Laughs] Tonight is Sushi night.
现在是寿司夜。
I'm feeling lucky.
感觉会转运。
Ben.
本。
No answer.
没回答。
Tom.
汤姆。
Ben?
本吗？
I'm coming down.
我来了。
Ben.
本。
Ben?
本吗？
Oh, tom.
噢，汤姆。
Oh, my God.
噢，我的天。
I can't believe he was down here the whole time.
我不能相信整个时间 死在楼下。
Yeah. Right below where our bedroom is.
是的。我们卧室下方。
Anna. What?
安娜。什么？
Oh, my God, tom.
噢，我的天，汤姆。
220,000 pounds.
220，000英磅。
What the hell was Ben doing with this much cash?
本哪来这么多现金吗？
What was he doing living in our basement with all this cash?
住我们楼下这么有钱？
Well, he was on disability,
噢，他残障，
and maybe he had a big settlement after an accident?
也许拿到了车祸赔赏？
I just don't know why it wouldn't be in the bank.
怎不放进银行。
So, what do we do?
我们该怎办？
Hm?
哼？
We call the police. Yeah?
报警，是吗？
Anna. Anna. What?
安娜，安娜。  什么？
Wait. [Doorbell rings]
等等。
Tom.
汤姆。
Help me. We shouldn't have brought this up here.
帮我把这塞好。
I know. You want to help me?
我明白。要帮我吗？
Tom. Help me now.
汤姆。  现在帮我。
I got it. Answer the door.
我了，开门。
Mr. Wright? Yes.
莱特先生吗？  是的。
I'm detective inspector John halden.
特勤探员 约翰霍尔顿。
So, Mr. Wright, what-what is it you do?
莱特先生 啥职业？
He's a landscape architect. Oh.
环境设计师。噢。
Yeah. I used to be, in Chicago.
是的。在芝加哥。
I had a small business, a little crew,
有个工作团队
but it fell apart in the crash,
解散了
so we moved here for a fresh start.
搬来这里重头起步。
We also had an unfortunate miscarriage a few years ago, so--
几年前算垮了，因此 --
oh, I'm so sorry. So sorry.
噢，非常抱歉。很抱歉。
It was a nice change for us.
是好的转机。
So, now I-I do contracting work
现在都接个案装修
odd jobs and manual labor.
跟体力劳动散工 。
Why London? Tom's renovating a house.
为何挑伦敦？汤姆翻新一所房子。
My grandmother passed a few years ago
祖母几年前的遗产
and we inherited the family house, so I thought I'd fix it up.
我们继承后 慢慢整理。
Good for you.
蛮好的。
So, Mrs. Wright, how are you, um, how are you liking London?
那莱特太太， 喜欢伦敦吗？
Anna, please.
叫我安娜。
I'm a school teacher at morningside primary school.
我是一个晨兴小学的老师。
My wife runs a clinic just down the street from there.
我妻子沿街不远有所门诊。
Sterling house? That's a, uh, women's shelter, right?
英币屋吗？妇女的辅导中心，是吧？
Yeah. They look after young women with drug addiction, take them off the streets.
是的。照顾年轻街头吸毒少女。
The government has withdrawn its funding, but they're hanging in there.
政府没经费但她们还窝在那。
My wife, Marie, isn't one for giving up.
我的妻子，玛丽，始终不放弃。
Anyhow...
总之
So, thank you for the tea.
谢谢你的茶。
It was very good.
很香。
How long have you been renting the room downstairs?
楼下租出去多久？
Uh, not long.
噢，不久。
I mean, we just did it 'cause we needed help with the rent.
是说才租出 需要拿来补贴。
Three months, maybe. Yeah.
是的 3 个月左右。
And he always paid by cash. Did you find this odd?
他都现金付租 不觉得古怪吗？
No, not really, no.
还好吧。
Did he, um,
是吗，嗯，
did he have any visitors?
有访客吗？
Uh, he really kept to himself. I mean, he didn't have much.
噢，他不太活动的。
No. He watched a lot of television.
都窝者看电视。
Yeah, that's true. Very loud.
是真的 非常大声。
Did, um, did you find anything unusual about him?
有发觉他异常吗？
When you, um,
嗯，是说你
when you discovered the body, did you--
发现尸体那时 --
did you find anything else?
有别的吗？
Um-- no.
嗯 -没有。
The reason I ask is because the initial police report
问这多是为了侦调报告
suggests that he died of a drug overdose,
主因死于毒品过量
and the team downstairs are just looking for evidence
楼下队员在搜证
that he may have kept drugs there.
他可能存放了些药。
No, we had-- I mean, we had no idea.
没，我们 -意思是不清楚。
Well, it's just, uh-- it's just routine.
嗯，没事--例行公事而已。
For your own safety.
为了你的安全。
[Newscaster] ...Late 40's
40年代的旧公寓
discovered in the basement of a flat.
地下室发现的尸首。
The cause of death is as yet unknown.
死因不详。
To the city now, and London's markets are still not steady.
现在伦敦市场仍然不稳定。
There's a new lead
有新的主管
to-to the guys that gave Julie the drugs.
替换提供毒品给朱莉的。
I thought Martin took you off that case.
马丁要你停手。
Yeah.
是的。
Is it dangerous?
危险吗？
Really dangerous, then.
那是真的危险。
Still not going to bring her back, John.
约翰 无法让她复活。
So,
因此
why take the risk?
何必冒险？
It might save someone else's daughter.
可以救其他人的女儿。
We'll call halden in the morning.
早晨打电话给霍尔顿。
Tom?
汤姆吗？
What are you doing?
在做什么？
We spent our whole lives being good, right?
我们求生活过的好点，对吧？
And what has it gotten us? Nothing.
但得到了啥？ 一无所有。
So, maybe this money is a gift to help us get our lives back on track.
或许这钱是一个礼物帮助我们上轨道。
Tom.
汤姆。
We don't know where this money comes from.
我们不知道钱的来源。
This could be really, really bad money.
很可能是脏钱。
I know.
我知道。
But what makes money bad?
啥让钱变脏的？
Not the money. The people make it bad.
不是钱 而是人。
What people do with it.
看人如何使用。
Now, I'm not saying we do anything rash.
我是说现在不急。
All I'm saying is we just wait and see.
是想静观变化。
He's been dead a week.
他死了一周。
The cops came, they didn't find anything.
警察来没找到任何东西。
No one's come forward looking for the money.
也没人出面讨钱。
Okay? And if they do,
对不？如果他们干的
this will look like Ben hid it.
本有意藏起来。
I say we just hide it
我是说  我们搁者
and wait a week.
等一礼拜。
Two weeks.
两礼拜。
All right.
好。
End of the month. And then
月底。  然后
nobody comes,
没人来，
we just find it again.
我们再次找到它。
Halden, where are the background checks on the Scott case?
霍尔顿，斯克特案调查在那里？
You wouldn't be wasting time on the Witkowski case? I told you to drop it.
别浪费时间在威特科斯基案？早说过别管了。
Nobody gives a shit if Jack Witkowski killed his twat of a brother.
没人在乎杰克．威特科斯基兄弟的死。
Another deficient shitsack off the street is fine with this department.
关掉出纰漏的街头对部门有益 。
The Scott background checks, on my desk by five.
斯克特身家调查 5 点前放我桌上。
And this has nothing to do with Julie?
让朱莉冤死吗？
No, no, no, no. It's just--
不，不。只不过的 --
it's just a hunch I want to follow up on.
是第六感  我想贯彻到底。
If I'm going to break every law I'm here to uphold,
如果我违反每条法律支援
I'd rather it was for a good cause.
宁愿有个高尚的目的。
Okay.
好。
It has everything to do with my daughter.
全都是为我女儿。
Bank accounts, inland revenue, utility bills, mortgage.
银行账户，国内税收，水电瓦斯费，抵押。
From now on, if Thomas or Anna Wright sneeze, you'll know about it.
现在汤马斯或者安娜有些许动静你都会知道。
But I warn you, there's not much money to follow.
但我警告你，没有经费。
No, not at the moment.
现在是没有。
Okay.
好。
You'll keep me posted?
不断向我提供消息吗？
If Martin finds out, I'll be fired.
如果马丁发现，我会下岗。
Martin's a smug little prick.
马丁是个小烂货。
Superintendent tosspot can go fuck himself.
陀斯波总长去狗日的自渎。
(Tom) Detective halden? Yes.
霍尔顿探长吗？  是的。
Hi, this is tom Wright from the--
嗨，我是汤姆莱特 --
how are you? We were just wondering
你好？  我们想知道
if you heard anything about the next of kin for Ben tuttle.
如果打听到本突塔亲属。
No, no, no. We haven't located any living relatives.
没 没。目前没活着的亲戚。
I just ask because, uh,
刚刚问是因为，噢，
we wanted to know what do with his things, his clothes and stuff.
怎处理他衣服物品。
No, no one's come forward, yet.
没人过问
Okay.
好。
And, uh, do you know, was it officially--
对了 官方报告 --
yeah, overdose.
是的，过剂量。
Looks like it was liquid o.
液态的。
What's liquid o? Heroin.
液体是什么？  海洛因。
I see. Wow.
哇 我明白了。
Okay. Have a good day. Bye.
好。整天顺利。  再见。
(Jack) You met my little brother, haven't you?
你遇见我弟弟， 对吧？
Always tried to let him win.
总让他赢。
Any game.
任何游戏。
Drove mom crazy.
让老妈发疯。
Said Bobby would never learn if we did that.
说那样 保比绝不会醒悟。
'Course she was right.
她没错。
Jack and Bobby. How it came to this?
杰克和保比怎走到这田地？
Mom was a fan.
妈妈过份溺爱。
She also had high expectations.
她期望过高。
Where's cousin Ben?
堂兄本住那里？
You know, when you recommend a guy,
当你推荐个小伙子，
you're tying his name to yours.
你脱不了牵连。
Did you know he was going to fuck me?
该知道他会窝里反？
If you tell me where I find him,
如果告诉我找到他，
maybe I'll choose to believe you on that.
比较信任你。
Eddie, sir, could I please trouble you for a pen?
埃迪先生，麻烦借支钢笔吗？
You done the right thing.
你做的对。
But that doesn't mean I'm not going to hold you accountable.
不代表你免责 我不容许。
Anna. Yeah.
安娜。  是的。
I spent some of the money.
我花掉些钱。
What?
什么？
The day we found Ben,
发现本当天，
the landlord gave us an eviction notice.
房东给我们搬家通知。
I was going to tell you, but you were in such a good mood,
当时气氛太好没提
and it was Sushi night.
寿司夜。
And then we found the money, and--
发现钱，和 --
I took just enough to keep the roof over our heads.
抵付了遮顶的家。
Look, we're in this.
迟早会这样。
As soon as we put the money in the oven and we didn't take it out, we were in this.
没人来讨取都会动用。
If we don't start paying off the mortgage, we're going to lose the house.
不然会失掉房子。
How do we do this?
怎么办？
We spend just enough to stop the bleeding.
只用到恰好为止。
We use cash where we can,
少许的现金
and we get Mike to write an invoice.
我们找麦克写张发票。
You want to bring Mike into this?
把麦克扯进来吗？
No, it's not like that. We're not bringing him into it.
不是要拉他。
But when I do a job for him, he usually pays me cash,
每次干活给我现金
and then writes an invoice.
都会打单子。
So, if anyone asks--
所以，有人问 --
right, there's a paper trail.
有据可查。
What if someone comes looking for it, tom?
汤姆 万一有人来讨钱 怎办？
Anna.
安娜。
Nobody's come.
不会的。
Nobody's going to come.
没人会来。
And if they do,
如果他们来
who's to say Ben didn't spend it?
能说本没花用吗？
How much are we talking?
结果花了多少？
Just enough to stay above water.
刚好不沾水。
The mortgage, credit cards.
贷款，信用卡。
Just so we're in the clear.
我们一身轻。
There's only one problem that I can think of.
只想到一个问题 。
What? You are going to be really lonely
什么？  你会很孤单
when the debt collectors stop calling.
讨款的停止催你。
Hi, this is Anna Wright. I'm calling to inquire about an appointment.
嗨，这是安娜．莱特。想挂个号。
Yeah, for an ivf consultation, if possible.
请教有关试管婴儿的事宜。
Hello.
你好。
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
狗日的，狗日的，狗日的。
Halden. It's Duncan.
霍尔登，是邓肯。
Yeah, what's up? Not much.
是的，怎回事？  不太多。
I'm calling 'cause we got a flag.
获报我们的监控。
The Americans? Yeah.
美国人吗？  是的。
You were right. A lot of activity today.
你对。  今天有些动作。
Mr. Wright made five separate payments.
莱特先生 理清了五处帐单。
I've got deposits to the current account, mortgage and credit cards.
活期存款，抵押款和信用卡。
Cash? Some cash. Some money transfers.
现金吗？  一些现金。一些钱转帐。
He spread it out. No single payment big enough to raise flags at the bank.
零星数笔不会引起银行注意。
Fuck.
狗日的。
We found the liquid o.
找到海洛因。
What about the cash?
现钞哩？
(Halden) Mr. Wright?
莱特先生吗？
Detective.
探长。
It looks like someone came for Ben's stuff after all.
有人来搜过本。
Yeah.
是的。
Who do you think would do this?
你认为谁干的？
Your tenant crossed a very bad man.
你的房客有损友。
That man's name is Jack Witkowski.
名字叫杰克．威特科斯基。
So, who called the police?
谁报警的？
No one.
没人。
I just wanted to talk to you.
刚好要跟你谈谈。
Yeah, well, why?
为什么？
Let's go upstairs.
我们上楼。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
It's not back there. It's in my car.
车还没回来 都在上头。
But I-I-I did just get an invoice from, um, Mike Calloway.
确实有些麦克科维的发票。
This Mike Calloway, he's a friend of yours?
麦克科维是你朋友吗？
He is, but I do a lot of work with him,
工作伙伴
and he owed me on two jobs,
还欠我两宗活
and we got paid upfront for this other thing last week.
上礼拜干完了别的工作。
If you're holding anything back,
假如你有隐情
you better tell me.
最好告诉我。
I don't quite understand.
我不懂。
The dead tenant, Ben tuttle, drug abuse,
死的房客，本突塔，滥用药物。
sudden activity in your bank account,
你银行账户突然有进出
and now, coincidentally, a break-in.
现在，又有闯空门。
I don't want to accuse you of anything.
不想指控你任何事情。
I just want to clarify things.
只想核实一下。
(Anna) You're welcome.
别客气。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey. Ouch.
嘿。  哎唷。
[Whispering] Sorry, I have to take this.
抱歉，先打完。
Would you do me a favor and please don't mention the break-in to my wife?
可以帮忙吗  别跟我妻子提闯空门？
She's been a little rattled since Ben died.
自从本死后她有点敏感。
No, really, it's fine.
不，真的，都过了。
Tom finally got paid on that big job I was telling you about.
汤姆完工拿到笔款 所以急者告诉你。
Oh, my God. I can't believe that.
噢，我的天。不敢相信。
Oh, no, that's too much.
噢，太好了。
Sarah, I got to go. Okay, bye.
莎拉，该挂了，再见。
So, this Mike Calloway, he pays you in cash?
是麦克科维，付了现金吗？
Sorry, what are you implying?
抱歉，暗示什么 ？
I'm implying nothing.
什么也没暗示。
I was inquiring about the deposit, and your husband cleared it up.
正在问你的丈夫清帐的事。
So, all's good.
算是好事。
The worst part is behind us, right, baby?
最坏的部分在后头，宝贝？
Yeah.
是的。
It's all good.
太顺利了。
Yo. Hey.
吁。  嘿。
Bloody hell. What?
见大头鬼了。  什么？
Quality stuff. Yeah.
好材料。 是的。
I thought you said you were going to lose your house.
以为你要赔掉房子。
Mike. Yeah.
麦克。 啥。
Can I tell you something?
能告诉你些事吗？
Hang on.
等下。
Sure. What kind of job?
当然。哪种工作？
Okay, I'm interested.
感兴趣。
Yeah, I'll come by with my partner.
是的，我跟伙伴过去。
Fine, I'll come alone.
好，单独。
Okay. See you then.
好。回见。
Looks like we might have another job.
我们可能 有别的工作。
(Tom) French guy, bought a big house in notting hill.
法国人，买罗庭小山的大房子。
Mr. Wright. Hi.
莱特先生  。  嗨。
Please take a seat. Thanks.
请坐。 谢啦。
You can call me tom. You're mister--
叫我汤姆。 先生大名 --
you must forgive me. English is not my first language.
原谅我。  英语不是我母语。
Okay.
好。
And you, you're American, yes? I am.
你是美国人，对吧？  我是。
I live here now. And you, you just moved to the area?
现在在这定居。你要搬过来？
I'm expanding my empire.
正扩大我的帝国。
Tell me, Mr. Wright, are you a team player?
莱特先生，你是队员吗？
I-I guess.
以为。
Do you want to talk about the renovations, mister...
要沟通装修的事，先生 ...
Genghis Khan.
成吉思汗。
Genghis Khan? Is that what you said?
成吉思汗？ 是说他？
Do you know this man?
认识这个人吗？
Uh, genghis Khan, yeah.
成吉思汗，是。 word by BEE
I mean, I've heard of him--
听说过他 --
he marched all over the world.
征服全世界。
Countries were so afraid of this man,
国际都怕这人
they would lay down their arms when they heard of his approach.
唯一只有投降。
Do you know what happened when they did that?
不然会怎样？
No, I don't know. Nothing.
我不知道。没什么。
Nothing happened.
没啥发生。
The great Khan welcomed them into his kingdom with open arms.
伟大的汗欢迎投诚的王国。
But those that resisted,
但是那些反抗的
felt his full fury.
让他狂怒。
He burned the cities, killed the men,
烧毁城市，灭族
raped their women, salted their crops.
强奸他们的妇女，伤口洒盐。
Okay.
好。
Um--
嗯 --
I'm sorry, I--
对不起，我 --
I think I'm probably not the right guy for this,
我不是合适的人，
so maybe you should get someone else for the renovations, okay?
你另找别人装潢？
Recently, a group of men stole from me.
最近，有人从我这偷取。
Where I come from, this would not happen.
在我家乡是不可能。
But I'm new here, so--
但初到贵地，因此 --
it's not the product that matters,
不单是护国问题
it's a question of honor.
是个荣誉
So now I'm burning cities,
现在燃烧城市，
I'm salting crops.
伤口抹盐。
And you have housed my enemy.
你收留我敌人。
Ben tuttle.
本突塔。
Oh, I see.
噢，明白了。
Okay, yes-- have you heard of Jack Witkowski?
好，是 -- 听过杰克．威特科斯基吗？
This man dishonored me.
这人玷辱我。
So, here's my question for you and your lovely wife, Anna.
想问你跟可爱的妻子，安娜。
Are you team players?
你们是团队吗？
What do you mean? Whose team are you on?
什么意思？谁的队？
I'm not on anybody's team.
我不属任何队。
If you're not on anybody's team,
如果你不是任何队，
you are not on my team.
也不是我的队。
So, whose team are you on?
那你在哪个队？
Detective halden, it's tom Wright.
霍尔顿探员，是汤姆莱特。
I need your help.
需要你的帮助。
Babe, it's me. Can you give me--
婴儿，是我。 我接手--
where's my money?
我的钱在那里？
I don't know what you're talking about.
不知道说啥。
Me and my brother's money.
我跟兄弟的钱。
Are you an idiot, you fucking cunt?
白痴，  你狗日的婊子？
And he died getting it.
他死在上头。
So, you can understand me wanting it back.
我必须讨回。
Now, where is it?
在那里？
[Whispering] I don't know.
不知道。
Please.
拜托。
Where's the money?
钱在那里？
So, that's how you want to play.
跟我玩。
It's fine with me.
对上胃口了。
[Echoing] I didn't want to go this far.
没想搞这套。
Please...
拜托...
Please, stop. Please.
请停止。拜托。
Where's my money?
我的钱在那里？
Please. Where's is it?
拜托。  在那里？
Please stop.
请停止。
Where's my money?
我的钱在那里？
Fuck!
狗日的！
Hm.
噢。
Anna.
安娜。
Anna, no.
安娜，不。
Welcome home, Mrs. Tommy.
欢迎你太太回家，汤米。
Tom.
汤姆。
[Whispering] The police are coming. Just stall.
警察会来。 拖延下。
I'm okay.
我知。
Oh, my God.
噢，我的天。
That's enough.
够了。
Get up.
起来。
Up!
站好！
This is what Tommy has.
汤米该受的。
Didn't you know? When you find a pot of gold,
当你发现金矿
there's always a monster guarding it.
总有怪物守护。
You smell so nice.
你闻起来真香。
Just relax.
别紧张。
Stop. It's downstairs.
住手。在楼下。
Bullshit. I looked all over.
扯 都找过。
It's in the window frame.
窗子框架里。
I hid it in the window frame.
我藏窗子框架。
Tom's lying.
汤姆说谎。
He's afraid that if he gives you the money, you're going to kill us.
怕给你钱，会杀我们。
Fuck.
狗日的。
Where's the fucking money?
狗日的钱在那？
Promise me you won't kill us.
答应我 不杀我们。
No.
好。
Stop pissing about.
别搓麻将。
Which one?
哪一个？
This one.
这。
It's this one.
这一阶。
Oh, fuck!
噢，狗日的！
(Tom) We're in here.
我们在这。
Downstairs. He's downstairs .
楼下。他在楼下。
(Halden) You're in serious trouble, Mr. and Mrs. Wright.
你遇到严重的麻烦，莱特先生及太太  。
You stole some money and you spent it,
偷了钱  又花了
so you're going to prison.
会蹲监狱。
Do we need to get a lawyer?
需要找律师吗？
A lawyer won't change that.
律师也改变不了。
Turning it in won't change it unless you can turn all of it in.
除了判刑谁都没法胜诉。
No, I didn't think so.
我不这样想。
And Jack Witkowski isn't the kind of guy to forgive and forget.
杰克．威特科斯基 是很记仇。
He'd find a way to get to you before we could even bring you to trial.
在我们庭审判前就做掉你。
I've tried to arrest him for two years.
努力逮捕他两年了。
He's got ties to the police.
跟警察挂勾。
Someone who turns a blind eye to what he does.
有人睁一眼闭一眼。
There are some people in Scotland yard that think
内应在苏格兰警场上级
that Jack is doing us a service.
杰克正帮忙外合。
He kills his fair share of bad people.
杀了分赃的坏人。
They believe that one in the hand is worth five in the street.
买通一个省五个街头的。
Think they can...Control him.
以为能控制他。
(Anna) But you don't.
但是你不会。
After he's paid off
当行贿后
whichever fucking corrupt coppers are protecting him,
哪个狗日腐败的靠山
he sells his stuff on the street at cut price.
街上贩毒分红。
He targets young women,
锁定年轻妇女，
single mums,
单亲妈妈，
people he thinks he can control.
大家以为他可掌握。
That's his specialty.
那是他的特长。
What? You help me, I'll help you.
什么？  你帮我，  我助你。
When Jack comes after you, we set a trap.
当杰克追上你，我们设陷阱。
How? You say he took your phone.
他带了你手机。
Yeah. When he calls,
是的。 他打电话时
you agree to take the money to him.
同意交钱。
You want to use us as bait?
拿我们作饵吗？
No.
不是。
All right, wait-- no.
好，等等 -- 不。
Just-- if we-if we do it, that means we walk. This doesn't go in the books.
那是让他感觉我们不吃这套了。
If I took this to headquarters, Jack would get wind of it,
如果我带款到总部，杰克会得知
I'd be out of a job, you two would be dead.
我失了业，你两死定了。
Find somewhere safe for tonight.
今晚躲在安全地方。
(Anna) Tom.
汤姆。
You know he would've killed you, right?
他会杀你，对吧？
You told me to stall. You told me the police were coming.
要我拖延。警察会到。
Before.
之前。
Why didn't you just show him where the money was?
为什么没让他看钱在哪？
Why didn't you tell me somebody broke into our house.
没告诉我有人闯进我们家。
I just wanted us to have a little money so we wouldn't get evicted,
只想弄点钱不被赶
so we could have-- [Pounding on wall] Shut up!
可能有 -- 闭嘴！
So we could have a life.
可改善生活。
I went to the fertility clinic,
我去过妇产院
and I spent some of the money.
也花了笔钱。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I feel so stupid.
我真蠢。
It's okay.
没事。
Something was wrong with me.
我们都犯错。
I just--
只不过 --
it's okay.
没事了。
Come here. Come here.
来这， 来。
All we wanted was a family.
只想求完整的家。
(Tom) It's him.
是他。
Hello?
你好吗？
(Jack) Knock, knock. Room service.
客房服务。
So, where have you put it? In the hotel safe or under the bed?
放在那里？  在饭店保险柜还是床下？
How can you fuck on that dirty mattress?
怎狗日的放脏褥垫？
People like you are so predictable, Tommy.
汤米 人都喜欢你可估计。
All right, you can have your money. Just leave us alone.
好，还你钱后别烦我们。
I want to see you and the money.
要见你带钱来。
When? Where?
什么时候？在那？
It needs to be in public for my safety.
为了我安全的公开场所
Tomorrow, noon, Victoria park by the pond.
明午，维多利亚公园池塘边。
And then you leave us alone.
事后别烦。
What now?
现在怎样？
The, um, the tracking device is sewn into the seam.
追踪器缝夹层。
It's virtually undetectable, and I can track you on my phone.
用我手机可监控。
As soon as you see him, put the bag down and walk away.
看见他，放下袋就走。
Don't run, don't look back.
别跑别回头。
No exceptions, no heroics, no nothing.
别有任何异样。
Just drop and go.
就放包走。
And when we're gone, you'll arrest him?
我离开，逮捕他吗？
Yes, as soon as he picks up the bag, it's over,
他一捡包全部结束
by which time you'll be gone and safe.
以后你安全了。
You'll be under constant supervision.
完全在监控下。
My men will be watching you, but you won't see them.
我的人看者你，你发现不了。
All right.
好。
Drop and go.
扔掉就走。
(Anna) He's going to get us killed.
他会杀我们。
(Tom) Not if we have back-up.
不会，我们有支援。
Bonjour. Enchantee.
幸会
You must be Anna.
你一定是安娜。
I take it Jack Witkowski paid you a visit.
杰克．威特科斯基拜访过你。
Yeah.
是的。
So, tell me, Mr. and Mrs. Wright,
莱特先生以及太太  ，
what is the plan you want to speak to me about?
告诉我计划内容？
Where is he?
他在那？
He'll call us.
会打电话给我们。
Where are you? You're late.
在那里？你晚了。
Tell me, Tommy, why are our good friends from the met joining us?
汤米我们的好朋友怎会参加？
Don't worry about him. He's not with us.
别担心他。我们不一起。
Just let him walk by and you can have your money.
只让他看到你取钱。
I'm not talking about that one, you tosser. He works for me.
不是说那个，他为我干活。
Wave to the good people, Marshall.
马歇尔跟好人招个手。
I'm talking about that mangy fuck, halden.
是指肮脏狗日的霍尔顿。
Run. Drop the bag.
跑。放下袋。
Fuck.
狗日的。
Marshall, you fucking dick, get the fucking money.
狗日的的马歇尔，笨B 抢狗日的钱。
Drop the bag, tom.
放下袋，汤姆。
Drop the bag.
放下袋。
Drop the bag. Run.
放下袋。  跑。
Anna, run.
安娜，跑。
(Anna) Why didn't you just drop the money?
怎没扔掉钱？
'Cause the money's the only thing keeping us alive right now.
钱让我们活到现在。
Halden is dead.
霍尔登死了。
I know.
我知道。
They killed him. I know.
他们杀了他。我知道。
Anna.
安娜。
What are we going to do, tom?
怎么办 汤姆？
Where are we going to go?
往哪躲？
We have one place where we can go.
我有个地方能去。
At least for a few hours.
至少几小时。
(Khan) You broke your word.
你不守诺言。
Do you think I would let you play me?
我会让你耍？
(Tom) I'm not trying to play you, Khan.
并没耍你 思汗。
When I find you,
当我找上你
just remember you brought this on yourselves.
别忘了你自找的。
Would you mind giving us a minute in private, Mrs. halden?
给我们一分钟密谈，霍尔顿太太？
Yeah, I was going to grab a coffee anyway.
反正我要喝杯咖啡。
What in God's name were you thinking?
天知道你怎回事？
Not only were you wearing a bulletproof vest,
穿防弹背心 word by BEE
but you took a firearm into a public park.
带手枪进公园。
There are children there, for Christ's sake.
到处是孩子 要命的。
You're an embarrassment.
你是累赘。
You should've retired when your junkie daughter died.
当毒虫女儿死就该退休了
[Nurse] Excuse me, sir. Mr. halden needs to rest.
先生，对不起。霍尔顿需要休息。
Okay, my apologies.
好，我道歉。
You rest up, John.
约翰 好好休息。
Good news for me is
好消息是
now I don't have to pay your pension.
现在我没必要给你养老金。
Who's going to pay your pension, ray?
谁付你的养老金，雷老板？
Scotland yard or guys like Jack Witkowski?
苏格兰场的家伙还是杰克．威特科斯基那种人？
I wanted to fix the floor before I showed it to you.
本想在你看到前修好地板。
It's a little different upstairs. You want to see?
楼上有点不同。想看看吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Remember when we started working on the house
记得我们哪时开始修房子
and we'd eat take-away on the floor?
坐地板吃外卖？
Yeah.
是的。
Remember when I thought I'd be done in four months?
本打算 4 个月完工？
Remember when I thought I'd be pregnant in six?
可记得我想6 个月怀孕吗？
I'm sorry I stopped coming here.
对不起  我都没来这这。
I'm sorry I got lost in this place.
对不起 我迷失在这里。
I never needed the house, tom.
汤姆我从未需要房子。
All I needed was us.
需要我们而已。
I know.
我知。
(Anna) We're going to make it.
我们会办到。
Tell me we're going to make it.
告诉我办得到。
It's okay, boo-boo. I'm coming.
乖乖 我来了。
Give me your phone.
给我你的电话。
Sarah?
莎拉吗？
(Jack) You smell so lovely.
你闻起来真可爱。
Julian's a real peach.
朱利安才是小樱桃。
Hello?
你好？
You want kids, don't you, Tommy?
想要孩子，对吧 汤米？
Me, too.
我也是。
Such a precious gift.
这宝贵的礼物。
So, hurting little Julian
伤害小朱利安
it's not going to be easy for me.
也不太忍。
He's so smooth.
如此光滑。
What's your plan, Tommy?
汤米，你怎么想？
We can't go out. After the park, the police are looking for us, too.
出不去，在公园之后警察到处找我。
We're hiding out in an old house in west London.
正藏伦敦西部外旧房子里。
I'll text you the address
传地址给你
and you come meet us here.
来这跟我们见面。
Okay?
好吗？
No more tricks.
别耍花样。
Keep fucking quiet.
保持狗日的安静。
Better text Khan.
也通知思汗。
Yeah.
对。
You really think he's going to come?
他会来吗？
It's all about honor with that guy.
那家伙注重荣誉。
Sent.
送。
You know they're going to have guns, right?
知道他们有枪，是吧？
Guns are for pussies.
娘泡才用枪。
Yeah.
是的。
(Jack) Look who's come for dinner.
看谁来晚餐。
Anna?
安娜？
Get ready.
准备好。
This is the perfect place.
完美的地方。
For what?
为什么？
I see no cash.
没看到现金。
It's in the house. Safe.
放房子里安全。
Don't fuck with me.
别狗日的弄我。
Jack, you can have the money
杰克，会拿到钱
just as soon as we get Sarah and Julian.
只要放给我莎拉跟朱利安。
Where's Mrs. Tommy?
汤米 太太在那里？
She's inside, with the money.
跟钱在里头。
What the fuck.
啥狗日的。
Honey, I'm home.
宝贝儿，我回家了。
Mrs. Tommy.
汤米太太。
You got five seconds to show me the money or I'm shooting your husband.
5 秒 内让我看钱 不然蹦你丈夫。
(Anna) The money's up here.
钱在上头。
How can I be sure?
怎能确定？
I just want Sarah, I want Julian,
我要莎拉，要朱利安，
but if you hurt them or my husband,
如果你伤害他们跟我丈夫
I will destroy all of it.
我都毁了。
That's impressive. I'll get them over.
给人深刻印象，来结束吧。
Get the fuck out, love.
带过来。
Now it's your turn.
该轮到你。
Well done, sweetheart.
干得好，情人。
Now the bag.
现在钱袋。
Jack?
杰克？
Are you all right?
还好吗？
Sarah!
莎拉！
Go out the ladder.
爬梯子。
[Whispering] Sarah, go out the ladder.
莎拉，梯子。
Oh, God. Give me Julian. Give me Julian
噢，上帝。  朱利安给我。朱利安给我
Andre?
安杜鲁？
(Khan) You betrayed me, Mr. Wright.
莱特先生 出卖我。
You cannot undo that.
你不能破坏。
You must be sacrificed pour le bien de tous.
为了补偿牺牲。
The greater good.
干的好。
Does not seem fair.
不太公平。
You are playing with toys while I am not playing at all.
你的玩具我没见过。
You are a worthy adversary.
好对手。
Ahh!
啊！
Anna.
安娜。
[Lady newscaster] Metro police today announced a breakthrough
今天铁路警局宣布一个突破
in a case that's traumatized people living in the sleepy London suburb of mortlake.
住伦敦郊区摩湖的居民遭受打击惊醒了睡着的大众。
It comes just 36 hours after a shootout which left five people dead
经历了36个小时枪战  5 人死亡
a house burnt to the ground, and the entire community in shock.
一所房子烧成灰烬，整个社区受到震撼。
With me is superintendent ray Martin,
访问的是警总长雷马丁
one of the officers in charge of the case.
办案的负责人。
Superintendent, what can you tell us?
长官，能告诉我们什么？
We can now confirm that these tragic events
现在能确认这些悲剧的事件
are directly linked to a drug turf war
争夺毒品战争
which began with an armed robbery that turned deadly in an east end night club .
从东方夜总会武装抢劫开始到致命的结束。
(Halden) Remarkable. Hi.
真精彩
...and extraordinary bravery of veteran detective John halden
特别英勇的老战士约翰霍尔顿探长
a man I consider to be a personal friend and a colleague.
我关心的朋友跟同事。
It's easy to be a hero when you're writing your own story.
当英雄很容易 编你自己的故事。
Uh, the firemen found this.
噢，消防队员找到这个。
It's, um--
嗯 --
it's not much, but, uh, it's yours.
虽微不足道，属于你的。
Good luck.
祝好运。
Hm.
噢。
(Tom) What took you so long?
干啥耽误那样久？
I just had to do one last thing.
必须办最后一件事。
All right. Say goodbye to this hell hole.
好。 跟鬼窝道别吧。
Come on.
来。
So, no more Sushi nights.
以后不用寿司夜了。
[Serena ryder singing "for you"]
＊每天